W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1766-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Baylor University Libraries
- Audiovisual Materials, 1766-1986, undated; 7
  - Slides, 1766-1984, undated; 3
    - Scott T. Poage and Traveler (dog) (11 slides), 1954-1971, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Robbie Lee and Scott A. Poage (14 slides), 1954-1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Robbie Lee and Scott A. Poage (19 slides), 1949-1969, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Houses (6 slides), 1967 April 16 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Houses (25 slides), 1959-1967, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Houses (8 slides), 1953-1959, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Family and Friends (17 slides), 1954-1967, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Family and Friends (25 slides), 1959-1973 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Family and Friends (25 slides), 1953-1973, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Family and Friends (13 slides), 1954-1966, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Lazy 'Leven Ranch (12 slides), 1965 March (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Lazy 'Leven Ranch (25 slides), 1965-1967 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Lazy 'Leven Ranch (25 slides), 1965-1967, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Lazy 'Leven Ranch (14 slides), 1966-1968 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified (3 slides), 1967, undated (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Singapore (8 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Singapore (2 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Malaya (16 slides), circa 1956 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Tbilisi, Soviet Union (6 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Tashkent, Soviet Union (1 slide), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Tashkent, Soviet Union (10 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Samarkand, Soviet Union (12 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Moscow, Soviet Union (3 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Moscow, Soviet Union (25 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 18)
    - Moscow, Soviet Union (3 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Tashkent, Soviet Union (22 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Tashkent, Soviet Union (9 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Moscow, Soviet Union (16 slides), circa 1959 (Box 196 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Moscow, Soviet Union (25 slides), circa 1959 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Moscow, Soviet Union (19 slides), circa 1959 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Rostov, Soviet Union (6 slides), circa 1959 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Rostov, Soviet Union (22 slides), circa 1959 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Bulgaria (3 slides), circa 1965 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Bulgaria (19 slides), circa 1965 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Turkey (6 slides), circa 1965 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Turkey (4 slides), circa 1965 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Hungary (2 slides), circa 1965 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Czechoslovakia (4 slides), circa 1965 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Romania (14 slides), circa 1965 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Southern Italy (1 slide), circa 1957 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Southern Italy (25 slides), circa 1957 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Southern Italy (3 slides), circa 1957 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Brussels, Belgium (22 slides), 1958 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Brussels, Belgium (8 slides), 1958 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Morocco (17 slides), 1958 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Morocco (9 slides), 1958 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Egypt (16 slides), 1965 November (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Egypt (25 slides), 1965 November (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Egypt (25 slides), 1965 November (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Egypt (25 slides), 1965 November (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Egypt (25 slides), 1965-1966 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Egypt (16 slides), 1965 December (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Canada (9 slides), 1965 September (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Canada (4 slides), 1965 September (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Tunis, Tunisia (9 slides), undated (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Ethiopia (12 slides), 1964, undated (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Ethiopia (25 slides), 1964, undated (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Brazil (25 slides), 1964 July (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Switzerland (24 slides), 1964 December (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 18)
    - Liechtenstein (1 slides), 1964 July (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 18)
    - Liechtenstein (3 slides), 1964 July (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Bolivia (22 slides), 1964-1970 (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Bolivia (25 slides), 1964, undated (Box 197 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Bolivia (25 slides), 1964, undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Bangkok, Thailand (25 slides), undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Bangkok, Thailand (5 slides), undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Somalia (13 slides), 1965 January (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Senegal (7 slides), 1958 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Senegal (15 slides), 1958 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Guinea (2 slides), 1958 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Congo (8 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Congo (2 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Nigeria (4 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - French West Africa (3 slides), undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Philippines (16 slides), 1971 September (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Philippines (4 slides), 1971 September (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Mauritius (21 slides), 1970 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Mauritius (1 slide), 1970 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Africa (24 slides), 1972 (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Africa (20 slides), 1972 February (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Rhodesia and Swaziland (5 slides), 1970 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Rhodesia and Swaziland (12 slides), 1970 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Southwest Africa (13 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Southwest Africa (7 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - South Africa (5 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Angola (2 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Mozambique (2 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Tanzania (9 slides), undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Tanzania (8 slides), undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Madagascar (17 slides), 1964, undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Madagascar (6 slides), undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Timbuktu, Mali (19 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Timbuktu, Mali (3 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Malia (12 slides), 1965 October (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Jerusalem, Israel (10 slides), 1964, undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Jerusalem, Israel (23 slides), 1964, undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Jordan (2 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Jordan (2 slides), 1965 January (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Congo (23 slides), 1958 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - Congo (7 slides), 1958 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Belgrade, Serbia (14 slides), 1963 September (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - Greenland (4 slides), 1962 September (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - South Pole (2 slides), 1962 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - New Zealand (13 slides), 1962 November (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Texas (10 slides), 1963-1964 (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 17)
    - Texas (25 slides), 1964-1965 (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 18)
    - Texas (5 slides), 1965 September (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Oregon (12 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Colorado (8 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 19)
    - Colorado (1 slide), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Florida (3 slides), 1964 July (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Canary Islands (11 slides), 1964 December (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Taby Poage (10 slides), undated (Box 198 OVZ, Folder 20)
    - Taby Poage (5 slides), undated (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Football (7 slides), 1963-1964 (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson (4 slides), 1964 April (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - John F. Kennedy’s Funeral (9 slides), 1963 November (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - John F. Kennedy’s Funeral (25 slides), 1963 November (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - John F. Kennedy’s Funeral (5 slides), 1963 November (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Unlabeled (20 slides), 1966-1967 (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Unlabeled (25 slides), 1967 June (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Unlabeled (25 slides), 1966-1967 (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Unlabeled (25 slides), 1963-1971, undated (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Unlabeled (25 slides), 1966 June (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Unlabeled (24 slides), 1964-1968 (Box 199 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Tapes, 1959-1986, undated; 4
    Subseries IV. Tapes houses audio tapes, film reels, and VHS tapes of W. R. Poage. All formats primarily relate to speeches Poage delivered to his constituents, often during reelection campaigns, and address topics such as predatory animals, care for the environment, the House Agriculture Committee, food prices, civil rights protests, the seniority system in Congress, student loans, Fort Hood, and Poage's retirement at the end of 1978.
    All of the materials in this subseries are digitized and located on a digital preservation server. The preservation identification numbers for each item are located in parentheses. Untitled materials have been reviewed and a basic description of the contents is included whenever possible. Please note there are a significant number of duplicates in this subseries, particularly in the audio tapes. In such instances, both copies have been kept and given unique preservation identification numbers. If you are interested in researching these materials, please contact the archivist for more details.
    - 3” Audio Reel, 2 30-Second Radio Spots, 60-Second Radio Spot, and 60-Second TV Spot (po-poage-rll 007), undated (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 3” Audio Reel, 2 30-Second TV Spots (po-poage-rll 003), undated (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 3” Audio Reel, 2 30-Second TV Spots (po-poage-rll 004), undated (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 3” Audio Reel, 2 30-Second TV Spots (po-poage-rll 005), undated (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 3” Audio Reel, 2 30-Second TV Spots (po-poage-rll 006), undated (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 3” Audio Reel, 60-Second TV Spot (po-poage-rll 001), undated (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 3” Audio Reel, 60-Second TV Spot (po-poage-rll 002), undated (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 3” Audio Reel, Address to Rotary Club of Houston (po-poage-rll 008), 1968 January 4 (Box 200 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 051) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 052) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 053) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 054) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 055) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 056) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 057) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 058) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 059) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, 1972 Campaign (po-poage-rll 060) (Box 201 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Compensation Regarding Losses Through Predatory Animals (po-poage-rll 035), 1972 May 21 (Box 202 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Compensation Regarding Losses Through Predatory Animals (po-poage-rll 036), 1972 May 21 (Box 202 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Concern About Ecology and Environment (po-poage-rll 045), 1972 July 23 (Box 202 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Concern About Ecology and Environment (po-poage-rll 046), 1972 July 23 (Box 202 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Current Legislation Handled by Agriculture Committee (po-poage-rll 029), 1972 April 30 (Box 202 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Current Legislation Handled by Agriculture Committee (po-poage-rll 030), 1972 April 30 (Box 202 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Meet the Member — W. R. Poage of Texas (po-poage-rll 063), 1969 March 7 (Box 202 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, New Proposals for Inaugurating and Financing Public Programs (po-poage-rll 033), 1972 May 14 (Box 203 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, New Proposals for Inaugurating and Financing Public Programs (po-poage-rll 034), 1972 May 14 (Box 203 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Observations Concerning Prospective Developments in Congress, Particularly as They Relate to the Agriculture Committee (po-poage-rll 009), 1972 January 30 (Box 203 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Observations Concerning Prospective Developments in Congress, Particularly as They Relate to the Agriculture Committee (po-poage-rll 010), 1972 January 30 (Box 203 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Price of Meats (po-poage-rll 031), 1972 May 7 (Box 203 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Price of Meats (po-poage-rll 032), 1972 May 7 (Box 203 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Proposed Reorganization of Executive Departments (po-poage-rll 037), 1972 May 28 (Box 203 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Proposed Reorganization of Executive Departments (po-poage-rll 038), 1972 May 28 (Box 204 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Protest Marches (po-poage-rll 022), 1972 April 2 (Box 204 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Protest Marches (po-poage-rll 023), 1972 April 2 (Box 204 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Renewal of Farm Legislation (po-poage-rll 047), 1972 July 30 (Box 204 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Renewal of Farm Legislation (po-poage-rll 048), 1972 July 30 (Box 204 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Return to the Good Old Days (po-poage-rll 027), 1972 April 23 (Box 204 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Return to the Good Old Days (po-poage-rll 027), 1972 April 23 (Box 204 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Rural Development Bill, 1972 Campaign Year (po-poage-rll 015), 1972 March 5 (Box 205 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Rural Development Bill, 1972 Campaign Year (po-poage-rll 016), 1972 March 5 (Box 205 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Seniority of a Member of Congress, Rank and Power on Committees (po-poage-rll 040), 1972 June 11 (Box 205 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Seniority of a Member of Congress, Rank and Power on Committees (po-poage-rll 041), 1972 June 11 (Box 205 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Sharp Increases in Food Prices (po-poage-rll 017), 1972 March 12 (Box 205 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Sharp Increases in Food Prices (po-poage-rll 018), 1972 March 12 (Box 205 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Student Loan Programs (po-poage-rll 025), 1972 April 10 (Box 205 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Student Loan Programs (po-poage-rll 026), 1972 April 10 (Box 206 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Congressional District Boundaries (po-poage-rll 011), 1972 February 6 (Box 206 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Importance of Fort Hood (po-poage-rll 012), 1972 February 13 (Box 206 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Seniority System in Congress (po-poage-rll 013), 1972 February 20 (Box 206 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Central Texas Parkway (po-poage-rll 014), 1972 February 27 (Box 206 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Predator Poison Control (po-poage-rll 019), 1972 March 19 (Box 206 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Drugs and Narcotics (po-poage-rll 020), 1972 March 26 (Box 206 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Untitled (po-poage-rll 021), 1972 March 26 (Box 207 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Changing Names and Structure of Federal Agencies (po-poage-rll 024), 1972 April 9 (Box 207 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Untitled (po-poage-rll 039), 1972 May 29 (Box 207 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Rural Development Bill (po-poage-rll 042), 1972 June 21 (Box 207 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Re-Enactment of Agricultural Act of 1970 (po-poage-rll 043), 1972 June 25 (Box 207 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Revenue Sharing Bill (po-poage-rll 044), 1972 July 2 (Box 207 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, August as Livestock Certification Month (po-poage-rll 049), 1972 August 6 (Box 207 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Radio Script, Types of Congressional Mail (po-poage-rll 050), 1972 August 13 (Box 208 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Retirement Speech (po-poage-rll 061), 1977 September 24 (Box 208 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 4” Audio Reel, Retirement Speech (po-poage-rll 062), 1977 September 24 (Box 208 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 5” Audio Reel, International Food Report, Program 13 (po-poage-rll 067), 1966 December 17 (Box 208 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 5” Audio Reel, Omnibus Farm Bill (po-poage-rll 068), 1965 (Box 208 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 5” Audio Reel, Retirement Speech (po-poage-rll 064), 1977 September 24 (Box 208 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 5” Audio Reel, Retirement Speech (po-poage-rll 065), 1977 September 24 (Box 208 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 5” Audio Reel, Postal Service Workers’ Wages (po-poage-rll 066), undated (Box 209 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Address at Washington Hilton (po-poage-rll 69), 1978 March 14 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Ceremony of Presentation of Congressional Resolution to Official Bearers of Nepalese Parliament (po-poage-rll 073), 1959 September 21 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Interview with Jack Burgess, KWBU-FM (po-poage-rll 072), 1976 October 13 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Poage Portrait Ceremony-Part 1 (po-poage-rll 070), 1968 February 26 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Poage Portrait Ceremony-Part 2 (po-poage-rll 071), 1968 February 26 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Poage Portrait Ceremony-Part 1 (po-poage-rll 074), 1968 February 26 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Poage Portrait Ceremony-Part 2 (po-poage-rll 075), 1968 February 26 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Poage Portrait Ceremony-Part 1 (po-poage-rll 076), 1968 February 26 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Poage Portrait Ceremony-Part 2 (po-poage-rll 075), 1968 February 26 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Representatives George Mahon and W. R. Poage (po-poage-rll 079), 1966 April (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Texas Academy of Honor in Agricultural Credit (po-poage-rll 080), 1969 March 8 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - 7” Audio Reel, Seniority of Legislators and Re-Election (po-poage-rll 078), undated (Box 209 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - 16 mm Film Reel, 1569 Poage Spot, House Recording Studios (po-poage-16m 082), 1967 January-February (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - 16 mm Film Reel, Footage of W. R. Poage in Washington, D.C. (po-poage-16m 086), circa 1960s and 1970s (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - 16 mm Film Reel, Footage of W. R. Poage Touring Facilities at Baylor University and Washington, D.C. (po-poage-16m 085), circa 1960s and 1970s (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - 16 mm Film Reel, Interview of Bob Poage as Chair of Agriculture Committee (po-poage-16m 084), circa 1967 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 15)
    - 16 mm Film Reel, Unveiling of Portrait for Chairman Bob Poage, House Agriculture Committee Room and Party (po-poage-16m 083), 1968 February 26 (Box 210 OVZ, Folder 16)
    - VHS Tape, “On Campus”, Representatives Bob Poage, O.C. Fisher, and Omar Burleson, ACU-TV, undated (Box 209 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - VHS Tape, Representative Bob Poage Speaking at Dedication of Poage Park in Woodway, 1986 August (Box 209 OVZ, Folder 4)